theuseful.com 2005-04-04

# Help Desk

Privacy Policy  

We respect your desire for Internet security and privacy, and have taken measures to protect your personal information. You can be assured that we take every measure to create a safe and enjoyable experience at Theuseful.com (Theuseful). This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how it is used. 

Our membership registration process requires that you provide us with basic contact information such as name, email, address and birthdate. Your personal information will be used to help us provide a better, more relevant experience. 

Minors under 18 years of age are not allowed to participate in any of the services and/or programs offered by Theuseful. No information should be submitted to, or posted at, any Theuseful Web sites by visitors under 18 years of age. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. 

Our site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Measures we take to uphold the security of user personal information includes, but is not limited to: Private network connection for database servers containing user information, user data encryption, and continuous monitoring of servers for intrusion with standby escalation procedures. 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. We allow you to control the email that you receive from us. In addition, our site provides its members the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out of receiving communications from third-party sponsors. 

If you request certain Theuseful services that are co-branded or require work performed by one of Theuseful's trusted partners, we do share membership information with our trusted content and commerce partners in order to fulfill your request and to provide you with the best possible member experience. Also, in the event that Theuseful or any of its assets are acquired by or merged with another entity, member information will be one of the transferred assets. 

When you register, you agree to to our Terms and Conditions and to receive information on special offers (eg coupons, gifts, discounts...) from Theuseful and other trusted partners whom may have access to your registration information and other relevant data in order to bring you valuable services. Theuseful's trusted partners agree to abide by their respective privacy policies. Theuseful and partners may send you information via various available channels and segmented lists. When you unsubscribe from one list, you will not be unsubscribed from all lists. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to enrich your user experience and to allow you to visit multiple pages of our site without having to login at every page. 

Our site contains links to other sites. Please note, however, that these other sites may have privacy policies that differ from those of Theuseful. We have no control over any personal information you choose to provide those sites. We provide the addresses of these web sites as an avenue of information for our visitors and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these web sites. 

By using this site, you agree to the Theuseful Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use or register at our site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Theuseful site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with Theuseful, please [contact us](http://www.theuseful.com/cs/?promo_name=).
